hi spring fans in this installment of
嗨，春季粉丝在本期中
spring tips we're going to look at how
春天的技巧，我们将看看如何
to test first api's microservice is in
测试第一个api的微服务在
effect first of all we're gonna build a
首先，我们要建立一个
new service so I'm going to build a
新服务，所以我要建立一个
service that's going to call the
将要调用的服务
customer service we'll use spring
客户服务我们将使用spring
support for building web applications
支持构建Web应用程序
will use JPA and h2 we use the verifier
将使用JPA和h2我们使用验证程序
the spring cloud contract verifier and
Spring Cloud Contract验证程序和
of course just to make my my tour a
当然只是为了我的旅行
little easier we're gonna use Lombok
我们将更容易使用龙目岛
which is a compile-time
这是一个编译时间
annotation processor well then Jen then
注释处理器好，然后仁
generate a new project which we can open
生成一个我们可以打开的新项目
up in our IDE so I'll do that now under
在我们的IDE中，所以我现在将在
customer service CD customer service
客户服务CD客户服务
Nautilus open this up
鹦鹉螺打开它
all right so now we have a new
好吧，现在我们有了一个新的
application and our application you know
应用程序和您知道的我们的应用程序
we should spread the test first right
我们应该先进行测试
keeping in good test trim practice we
保持良好的测试修剪习惯，我们
should write the test first so let's say
应该先写测试，所以说
that we have a new API and when we call
我们有一个新的API，当我们调用
this the customer rest controller test
此客户 rest controller 测试
all right so this is a new test we're
好的，这是我们的新测试
gonna use the spring boot test framework
将使用Spring Boot测试框架
we're gonna run with the spring runner
我们要和春跑者一起跑步
right this is the spring runner that
对，这是春天跑步者
works with J Unit four and five this is
与J单元4和5合作，这是
going to be a spring boot test that will
将是一个 spring boot 测试，
work with a mock weather environment so
在模拟天气环境中工作，因此
we'll say a mock and I think that's it
我们会说一个模拟，我想就是这样
for now that'll be okay we want to use
现在就可以了，我们要使用
the mock can BC support and spring
模拟可以BC支持和春天
spring boots we'll use that as well and
spring boot 我们也会用
that'll allow us to auto wire and mock
这样我们就可以自动连线和模拟
MVC client here and the mock can be C
MVC客户端在这里，模拟可以是C
client we can actually work with to
我们可以与之合作的客户
issue requests against the database so
对数据库发出请求，因此
we'll say public void should return all
我们会说公共虚空应该归还所有
customers so we're gonna have an
客户，我们将有一个
endpoint here that we think will return
我们认为将返回的端点
all customer data right so we can say
所有客户数据正确，所以我们可以说
this mock NB C dot perform mock MVC
这个模拟NB C点执行模拟MVC
result matures dot get I'm sorry request
结果成熟点得到我很抱歉的请求
mattress mock MVC request mattress
床垫模拟MVC请求床垫
builders dot get I'm gonna say we make
建设者点得到我要说我们做
it post to the to it make it get to the
它发布到它使其到达
guest you get customers in point and
来宾，您会吸引客户，并
we're going to accept it when to send a
我们将在何时发送
content type well we don't actually care
我们实际上不在乎的内容类型
so we'll that's fine we're gonna expect
所以我们会没事的
certain things back right so I'm going
某些事情回来了，所以我要走了
to say a mock MVC result matters that
说一个模拟MVC结果很重要
status will be okay no problem and we're
状态不会有问题，我们
going to expect that the content type
期望内容类型
will be well-known it'll be a media type
将是众所周知的它将是一种媒体类型
application JSON utf-8 for example and
应用程序JSON utf-8例如，
what else do we want to say we want to
我们还要说什么我们想
say that this throws an exception
说这引发异常
that'll solve this and I think we should
可以解决这个问题，我认为我们应该
also you know have a have a description
你也知道有一个描述
about what the shape of the payload
关于有效载荷的形状
should be when it comes back so we're
应该是回来的时候，所以我们
gonna say that we expect the the
要说我们期望
payloads to match a JSON path so I'm
有效负载以匹配JSON路径，所以我
gonna say mark MVC result
要说标记MVC结果
content dot JSON path and then you know
内容点JSON路径，然后您知道
we can even use a JSON matric we can say
我们甚至可以使用JSON矩阵
JSON path like this and that's what
像这样的JSON路径就是这样
we're gonna do is so we're gonna say at
我们要去做，所以我们要在
dot let's say the first record dot what
点让我们说第一个记录点
what do I say when I say ID equals one
我说ID等于1时该怎么说
right we'll say equals one and equals
对，我们会说等于一等于
that is not empty value there we go one
那不是空值，我们去一个
and we can also say that the first name
我们也可以说名字
or it may be the let's just say name
或是说名字
okay so the name will be equal to Bob
好吧，这个名字就等于鲍勃
okay or Jane there we go nice and good
好吧，或者简，我们走得很好
so we haven't a name there and we have
所以我们在那里没有名字，我们有
now just we've asserted some basic
现在我们已经断言了一些基本的
things about the structure we're
关于我们的结构的事情
assuming that's you know the syntax here
假设你知道这里的语法
means look into the jason that comes
意思是看进来的杰森
back it's gonna be an array
返回它将是一个数组
this means traverse all the arrays and
这意味着遍历所有数组，
run a predicate we're gonna dereference
运行一个谓词，我们将取消引用
the first element that comes back on in
再次出现的第一个元素
the in the array and we're gonna assert
在数组中，我们要断言
that the first record should be jane and
第一个记录应该是简和
that the content that comes back will be
回来的内容将是
of type application JSON so let's run
类型为JSON的应用程序，让我们运行
this code to see what we get okay so run
这段代码看看我们能做什么，所以运行
run run and of course this is going to
运行运行，当然这将
fail pretty catastrophic Lee we've
失败了灾难性的李我们
written more tests than we need to get
写了比我们需要更多的测试
to that point but we do know that this
至此，但我们确实知道
is going to fail so now it's our job to
将会失败，所以现在这是我们的工作
implement the production code make sure
实施生产代码，确保
that this kind of works right and
这种工作是正确的，
normally in Testament development you'd
通常在《圣经》发展中
you should only like write a single test
你只想写一个测试
it returns okay then you go back to the
它返回好，然后您返回到
production code and you you make it
生产代码，您就可以做到
return okay and then it says okay I'm
返回好，然后它说好，我
gonna return JSON application J's and
将返回JSON应用程序J和
then you make sure that returns as you
那么您要确保返回的结果与您一样
expect and you know you go back and
期待，你知道你回去
forth but let's let me just skip ahead
来吧，但让我跳过
here a little bit I'm gonna write the
这里我要写一点
test for one sort of what I expect to be
测试我所期望的一种
the minimum sort of feature set for this
为此设置的最小功能集
end point so let's go back now to the
结束点，让我们现在回到
customer risk controller which we don't
我们没有的客户风险控制者
have right so we're gonna have to go
正确，所以我们必须走
back to our code will go here and we'll
回到我们的代码将在这里，我们将
say source main Java comm example
说出主要的Java comm示例
customer service insert customer rest
客户服务插入客户休息
controller
控制者
and we'll insert the rest controller
我们将插入剩下的控制器
like so we'll say at risk controller and
就像这样，我们将在风险控制人员处说
we'll have some end points here we're
我们这里有一些终点
gonna say that we're gonna have an end
要说我们将要结束
point that returns customers it's gonna
返回客户的点
return a collection of customer records
返回客户记录的集合
so we expect so there's that and already
所以我们希望有
we've gotten into some trouble we need
我们遇到了一些我们需要的麻烦
some customer data right so we can say
一些客户数据，所以我们可以说
get all customers we need a customer
获得所有客户我们需要一个客户
record so let's assume that this is a
记录，所以我们假设这是一个
JPA entity it'll have a primary key long
JPA实体它将有一个长主键
ID at ID at generator value and I'll
ID为生成器值的ID，我将
have a string
有一个字符串
alright and what did we say in the test
好吧，我们在测试中说了什么
the test will the test looks for name
测试将测试名称
that's our name okay so we're gonna
那是我们的名字好吧，我们要
expect that to be their string name all
希望这是他们的所有字符串名称
right so there we go there's our basic
对，所以我们去那里是我们的基本
entity now of course this requires
现在的实体当然需要
Gators and setter so I'll use Lombok to
鳄鱼和二传手，所以我要用龙目岛
create that for me and there we are okay
为我创造那个，我们可以
so we've now got two entities here and
所以我们现在有两个实体
now we can we can implement this now we
现在我们可以执行此操作了
know that we're gonna need to be able to
知道我们将需要能够
persist data into the database so we
将数据持久保存到数据库中，因此我们
should use spring data JPA here we're
应该在这里使用spring数据JPA
gonna create a Java class a customer
会创建一个Java类的客户
repository alright and this is actually
好的仓库，这实际上是
not in a class it's gonna be an
不在课堂上，它将是一个
interface and the interface well that's
界面和界面很好
enough that's actually enough to get
足以足以获得
what we know is what we want so now we
我们知道的是我们想要的，所以现在我们
can inject that repository here private
可以将该存储库注入此处私有
final customer repository and dear from
最终客户资料库和亲爱的
set from the constructor and then return
从构造函数设置然后返回
this customer pause for defined all
该客户暂停所有已定义的
right so we have to actually extend JPA
对，所以我们必须实际扩展JPA
repository for this to work all right
可以正常工作的存储库
very good so very basic interface there
非常好，所以那里的基本界面
and this makes it so that we have
这使得我们有
declarative data management
声明式数据管理
functionality we provide it
我们提供的功能
out-of-the-box thanks to spring data JPA
借助Spring数据JPA开箱即用
which means that we can go back to our
这意味着我们可以回到我们的
tests here they test and let's see what
测试这里他们测试，让我们看看
happens
发生
and of course this is gonna fail as well
当然这也会失败
first of all assuming it works I and I
首先，假设我和我都可以
think it should work but yeah basically
认为它应该工作，但是是的，基本上
we expected a certain set of data to be
我们期望有一定的数据集
in the results and of course there is no
结果中当然没有
data so what we need to do is to mock
数据，所以我们需要做的是模拟
out the date access layer which makes
出日期访问层，这使得
sense what we're trying to test here in
感觉我们正在尝试在这里进行测试
this layer is our interaction with not
这层是我们与
with the database but with the rest
与数据库，但与其余
endpoint we're trying to assert that
端点，我们试图断言
given a request of a certain shape that
给定某种形状的要求
we get a response of a certain shape
我们得到某种形状的反应
back so let's use the spring boot test
返回，让我们使用spring boot测试
frameworks support for mock beans
框架支持模拟 bean
basically we can inject the customer
基本上我们可以注入客户
repository but of course spring our boot
存储库，但当然会启动我们的靴子
already sees that we have a real
已经看到我们有一个真正的
customer posit Ori so what this mock be
客户假设Ori，那么这个模拟会是什么
an annotation says is prepare a mock
注释说准备模拟
object using mockito
使用模仿对象
and then let the client that's ask the
然后让询问的客户
tester let us prepare a mock object in
测试器让我们在其中准备一个模拟对象
our test and then replace any pointers
我们的测试，然后替换任何指针
to this this this repository in the
为此，此存储库中的
application context with the mock
模拟的应用程序上下文
version that we're gonna configure here
我们将在此处配置的版本
right so let's configure it so that it's
好的，让我们对其进行配置，以便
not just a mock it's actually a stub
不只是一个模拟，它实际上是一个存根
it'll you know it'll return certain data
你会知道它将返回某些数据
when asked you know it's gonna follow
当被问到你知道它会跟随
our protocol so this customer posited it
我们的协议，因此该客户提出了
findall then return and win return an
findall然后返回并赢得返回
ArrayList of customers right so a new
ArrayList的客户对，所以很新
customer the first one will be Jane
客户的第一个将是简
second one will be Bob and there we go
第二个人是鲍勃，我们去了
okay so we've got some records in the
好的，所以我们在其中有一些记录
results that come back now we have you
现在回来的结果我们有你
know we haven't had to do a lot of extra
知道我们不必做很多额外的事情
work here right spring is just smart
在这里工作春天很聪明
enough to know to replace the the real
足以知道取代真实
thing with this mock version for the
这个模拟版本的东西
specific purposes of this test and that
该测试的特定目的以及
seems that worked so we've got you know
似乎有效，所以我们知道了
it's working as we expect we can also
正如我们期望的那样，它还在工作
prove a negative by by tampering with a
通过篡改
test here we can prove that the test was
在这里测试，我们可以证明测试是
working by breaking the test just in
通过打破测试来工作
case you never know so that is working
如果你永远不知道那是可行的
as we expect so good so we're now in a
正如我们所期望的那样好，所以我们现在处于
good situation now we've got a service
好的情况，现在我们有服务了
let's go build the client let's go build
让我们去建立客户让我们去建立
a client to talk to this service all
客户与所有服务进行交谈
right so we're going to build a new
对，所以我们要建立一个新的
client here it starts out spring that
客户在这里从春天开始
i/o I'm going to call this customer
我要打电话给这个客户
client and in this case we don't need
客户，在这种情况下，我们不需要
the JPA support nor do we knew the h2
JPA支持，我们也不知道H2
support but we can use this stubborn er
支持，但我们可以使用这个固执的人
here so we'll use spring cloud contract
在这里，我们将使用Spring Cloud Contract
step runner and otherwise looks fine to
踩跑者，否则看起来很好
me so we'll generate that and that'll
我，所以我们将产生那个
give us a new project so we'll go to our
给我们一个新项目，所以我们去
downloads directory unzip this extract
下载目录解压此摘录
the files ok customer client open that
好的客户客户的文件打开
up and open this up and now the customer
打开并打开，现在是客户
client is going to be the client API
客户端将成为客户端API
that client that others can use to talk
别人可以用来交谈的那个客户
to that service you know we can have a
您知道我们可以为您提供这项服务
lot of discussions about how much magic
关于多少魔法的很多讨论
should there be in the code for that and
该代码中是否应该包含和
all that but for our purposes let's just
所有这些，但出于我们的目的，我们只是
let's just build a simple client and
让我们建立一个简单的客户端，
make sure that there's no magic in it
确保里面没有魔术
and then it's a the service itself
然后是服务本身
stands on its own and other languages
自己和其他语言站立
and other protocols can can use it with
其他协议可以将其与
impunity but for our purposes let's just
有罪不罚，但就我们的目的而言，
do that you know we'll write some code
你知道我们会写一些代码吗
here to make it as simple as possible
在这里使其尽可能简单
right so we have a package as usual and
对，所以我们像往常一样有一个包裹
we'll build a customer client object
我们将建立一个客户客户对象
okay and in the client object we know
好的，在客户端对象中，我们知道
that we're gonna have a test so let's go
我们要进行测试，所以让我们开始吧
test this we're gonna create create a
测试一下，我们将创建一个
new test here for the customer client
客户客户的新测试
test and we'll have a we'll have
测试，我们将拥有一个
intelligence help us with that right
情报帮助我们实现这项权利
synchronizing our code there and so in
在那里同步我们的代码
the test we're gonna use the same
我们将使用相同的测试
mechanisms as before it's gonna be a
像以前一样的机制
spring boot test we're gonna run it with
spring boot 测试，我们将与
the spring runner class this is going to
春季跑步者班
use the customer client application
使用客户客户应用程序
though hopefully for most of your
虽然希望对您大多数人来说
clients you use Auto configuration so
使用自动配置的客户端
that spring boot consumers can just add
spring boot 消费者可以添加
the library to the past path and the
图书馆过去的道路和
bean will get registered in the
Bean将在
application context but for our purposes
应用程序上下文，但出于我们的目的
let's say that we've just got a manual
假设我们只有一本手册
pointer to an application context
指向应用程序上下文的指针
somewhere and we've got a configuration
某个地方，我们有一个配置
class so I'm going to define a test that
类，所以我将定义一个测试
tests our interaction with the customer
测试我们与客户的互动
service ok client should return there we
服务还可以，客户应该回到我们那里
are
是
so throws exception and in the code
因此引发异常，并在代码中
we're going to need the
我们将需要
the customer client so let's inject that
客户客户，所以让我们注入
here of course private customer client
这里当然是私人客户客户
all right not bad so now we say BDD
不错，所以现在我们说BDD
assertion stop then this dot client dot
断言停止，然后此点客户端点
dot what right where's the method to get
点正确的方法在哪里
all customers well that's not gonna work
所有客户都行得通
so the first thing we need to do is to
所以我们要做的第一件事是
create that method right get all
正确创建该方法
customers and we're gonna return a
客户，我们将返回一个
collection of what customer right we
收集什么客户权利我们
need a customer as well so we we need to
也需要一个客户，所以我们需要
create that DTO that representation
创建那个DTO那个表示
there let's just create it in line all
在那里，我们将其全部创建
right we can say at data and we'll give
对，我们可以对数据说，我们会给
it a we know it's a long ID and a
我们知道这是一个长ID和一个
private string surname all right so
私有字符串姓好
there we go there's our DTO and in order
我们去那里是我们的DTO，
for this to work you know we can return
为了这个工作，你知道我们可以返回
a new ArrayList just for now just to see
现在只看一个新的ArrayList
how much of the test we can get to
我们可以参加多少测试
passed there we go so now it's back to
通过那里，我们走了，所以现在回到
working then we can say that the size is
工作，那么我们可以说大小是
equal to two so let's say that there's
等于两个，所以说
two records coming back okay let's see
两个记录又回来了，好吧，让我们看看
if that works
如果可行
well of course that didn't work right
当然，这是行不通的
several reasons first of all this
首先有几个原因
application this web application is just
该Web应用程序只是应用程序
added to web application so we need to
已添加到Web应用程序中，因此我们需要
make sure it doesn't start up on port
确保它不会在端口上启动
as well and the other thing is we don't
以及另一件事是我们不
have this beam configured anyway right
无论如何都要配置这个光束
this is not registered in application
这没有在应用程序中注册
context it's not a component so we need
上下文不是组件，所以我们需要
to have that in the configuration here
在这里的配置中
so we can we can go here create a new
所以我们可以去这里创建一个新的
customer client configuration customer
客户客户配置客户
client configuration and we'll move the
客户端配置，我们将移动
customer out to its own type as well
客户也可以选择自己的类型
there we are
我们在那里
customer client configuration will live
客户客户端配置将生效
here and we'll register the customer
在这里，我们将注册客户
client right all right so return new
客户没事，所以还可以
customer client very good and now we've
客户客户很好，现在我们已经
got a simple service let's let's now try
有一个简单的服务，让我们现在尝试
that customer client code again well the
该客户客户代码再次很好
test work this time somehow I doubt it
这次以某种方式测试工作，我对此表示怀疑
but we can try ok that failed again
但是我们可以尝试再次失败的确定
right and this this time it's failing
对的，这一次失败了
from more realist you know reasonable
从更多现实主义者那里你知道合理
reasons we're returning zero but it's
我们返回零的原因，但这是
expecting two so now we need to to
期待两个，所以现在我们需要
actually implement enough meat of this
实际实施足够的肉
test of this client rather so that we
测试此客户，而不是让我们
can get what we're trying to get done
可以得到我们想要完成的事情
done
做完了
right we need the rest template so we
对，我们需要其余的模板，所以我们
can make a call right so there we go and
可以打电话给我们，然后我们去
inject that into the codebase and of
注入到代码库和
course this implies that we're going to
当然，这意味着我们要
need a configuration for that rest
其余需要配置
template so let's create that here we'll
模板，所以让我们在这里创建
say at beam rest template returning new
说在梁休息模板返回新
rest template like so and we'll inject
像这样休息模板，我们将注入
the rest template there rest template RT
其余模板在那里其余模板RT
there we are now we're cooking so now we
我们现在在这里做饭，所以现在我们
have a rest template and we have the
有一个休息模板，我们有
customer client and the client test is
客户客户和客户测试是
going to return some data based on a
将基于返回一个数据
call to a web service so let's write
调用网络服务，让我们写
that code here instead of returning an
该代码在这里，而不是返回一个
empty array list we can say this dot
空数组列表，我们可以说这个点
this template dot exchange HTTP
此模板点交换HTTP
localhost 8080 forward slash customers
本地主机8080正斜杠客户
right so we know that's going to be nice
对，所以我们知道那会很好
to be get call and
接到电话
that we're not gonna send any data to
我们不会发送任何数据给
the service and we know that we need to
服务，我们知道我们需要
tell the rest template what kind of data
告诉其余模板什么样的数据
we want back so we're gonna say well a
我们要回来，所以我们要说一个
collection of customer data right PTR
收集客户数据权PTR
equals new parameterize type reference
等于新的参数化类型引用
of type collection of customer okay so
客户的类型集合可以吗
now that that super type took an
现在那个超级类型花了
implementation gives us everything we
实施为我们提供了一切
need to to then return the data back so
然后需要将数据返回
we can we can put that in here and do
我们可以把它放在这里做
you reference the response so get a
您引用响应，因此得到一个
response entity with a payload of type
有效载荷类型为响应实体
collection of customer and then we can
收集客户，然后我们可以
then do you reference the body which is
那你参考的身体是
here and we're off all right we've got
在这里，我们没事了，我们有
the the payload and everything we're
有效载荷和我们所需要的一切
good now there's some discussion there's
好，现在有一些讨论，
some argument to be made that we could
有人提出我们可以
be using you know Thane or something
正在使用你知道塔恩之类的东西
more succinct in this case but for our
在这种情况下更简洁，但对于我们
purposes it suffices to leave things as
目的足以将事物保留为
they are so now we've got an actual
所以现在我们有了一个实际的
service and we can try this alright
服务，我们可以尝试一下
let's see one more time we've got an
让我们再看一次
actual client rather we can try this now
实际的客户，我们现在可以尝试
all right that failed yet again and I
好吧，那又一次失败了，我
think you can guess why there's no
想你能猜出为什么没有
service
服务
right and this is actually the the
对，这实际上是
problem if you will with microservices
问题，如果您愿意使用微服务
in order for us to test this effectively
为了让我们有效地测试
in order for us to effectively test the
为了我们有效地测试
boundary of this of this client rather I
这个客户的边界，而不是我
need to have the API so ok right I don't
需要有API，好吧，我不需要
want to actually stand up all my api's
想真正站起来我所有的api
each time I want to run tests that would
每次我想运行测试时
mean that all of my unit tests now
意味着我现在所有的单元测试
become integration tests when I move to
当我搬到
the world of micro services that sounds
听起来微服务的世界
like a non-starter because I'd very
像初学者一样，因为我非常
quickly end up in a situation where I
很快就遇到了我
have to wait 20-30 minutes just to
不得不等20-30分钟
deploy and just to integrate you know my
部署并只是整合您就知道我
simple client right that that's a
简单的客户权利，那就是
non-starter and it gets even worse if
没有起步，如果变得更糟
you talk about the poor html5 and iPhone
你说的是可怜的html5和iPhone
and Android developers who have to who
和谁需要谁的Android开发人员
would have to in theory deploy the whole
理论上将不得不部署整个
system just to be able to test the code
系统只是为了能够测试代码
that they're writing for the client
他们正在为客户写信
experiences right so we need to we need
体验正确，所以我们需要
to synthesize that if here this is you
综合起来，如果这是你
know we can we can't expect every client
知道我们可以期待所有客户
of every service to run every other
每个服务的运行彼此
service and all the dependent services
服务和所有相关服务
just to be able to to go through the
只是为了能够通过
continuous integration environment
持续整合环境
remember the whole point of micro
记住微点
services is to optimize for agility to
服务是为了优化敏捷性
gain the speed
加快速度
change and if we lose that by giving up
变化，如果我们放弃放弃
our ability to quickly test and get fast
我们快速测试并快速获得能力
feedback then what's the point exactly
反馈，那么到底有什么意义
right we want to make sure we have that
对，我们要确保我们拥有
fast feedback so okay let's mock out the
快速的反馈，好吧，让我们模拟一下
API and here we can take advantage in
API，在这里我们可以利用
the customer client test of wire mock
电线模拟的客户客户测试
right we can Auto configure wire mock
好的，我们可以自动配置电线模拟
this is part of spring cloud contract
这是Spring Cloud合同的一部分
and this is great for api's that we
这对于api来说很棒，
don't control right we if we know it's
如果我们知道这是不控制的权利
an API that's stable and we don't have
一个稳定的API，我们没有
the ability to control that service then
然后控制该服务的能力
we can use wire mock to build a fake API
我们可以使用电线模拟来构建假API
for us so we're gonna say so our mocks
为了我们，所以我们要说的是我们的模拟
dub for wire mock dot URL equal to wire
电线模拟点URL的复制等于电线
mock sorry were mocked I can get okay
嘲笑对不起被嘲笑我可以好起来的
why mock URL equals to customers and
为什么模拟网址等于客户，并且
what else did we say the client needs so
我们还说客户还有什么需要
the client needs it should be get
客户需求应该得到
customers some port 8081 let's make it
客户一些端口8081让我们做到
on 8081 we know the service will be on
在8081上，我们知道服务将会开启
so i'm gonna configure wire mock to
所以我要配置电线模拟
start on port 8081 okay there are and
从8081端口开始好的，还有
what else do we need we know that the
我们还需要什么，我们知道
payload that comes back will be will be
回来的有效载荷将是
a collection of customers as JSON right
作为JSON的一组客户
so we're gonna we're customers client is
所以我们要成为客户客户是
using the rest template and restaurant
使用其余的模板和餐厅
it's gonna convert the data into a
它将数据转换为
collection of customer entities of type
类型的客户实体集合
JSON so ID and surname all right all
JSON，所以ID和姓都可以
right so let's try this we're gonna now
对，所以让我们尝试一下，现在
return a response wire mock dot a
返回响应线模拟点a
response and the response dot will have
响应和响应点将具有
a body and I'll have a status code of
身体，我的状态码为
type 200 naturally because it's gonna be
自然地输入200，因为它将
great and we're gonna have a body and
太好了，我们会有一个身体
now we could pass in a byte array we can
现在我们可以传入一个字节数组
pass in a string you know and this is
传入您知道的字符串，这是
where it becomes very useful to have the
在这里变得非常有用
support for auto for testing JSON inside
支持自动测试内部的JSON
of a spring test dream spring loop test
弹簧测试的梦想弹簧环测试
framework here we can inject a object
框架在这里我们可以注入一个对象
mapper and use that to a great effect to
映射器，并用它来产生很大的效果
just get some JSON for some customer
为一些客户获取一些JSON
records okay so if customer customer
记录好，所以如果客户客户
customers okay so what we're gonna do is
客户很好，所以我们要做的是
we're gonna create an ArrayList arrays
我们将创建一个ArrayList数组
dot as lists for these customers and
点作为这些客户的列表，以及
turn that into JSON using this object
使用此对象将其转换为JSON
mapper dot right value is string
映射器点右值是字符串
customer list etc and this of course
客户名单等，这当然
throws an exception so we'll say throw
抛出异常，所以我们说抛出
exception very good so there's our
异常非常好，所以我们有
customer list and we're just gonna use
客户列表，我们将使用
that that custom method there to return
该自定义方法在那里返回
the data so the body will be JSON for
数据，因此主体将为JSON
customer and I'm gonna return to
客户，我要回到
customers we know that were expecting
我们知道的客户
what did we say we're expecting well we
我们说了什么我们期望很好
have one got two records right it only
只有一张有两张唱片
says we need to code two customers so
说我们需要编码两个客户，所以
let's say we've got two customers I
假设我们有两个客户
think we need a constructor for this to
认为我们需要一个构造函数来
be kind of fun so all argument
有点有趣，所以所有争论
constructor no argument constructor very
构造函数无参数构造函数
good and we're gonna pass in a ID one
好，我们要传递一个ID
and the first name will be Jane and the
而名字叫Jane和
second one will be Bob okay so there's
第二个是鲍勃，好吧，
our two records and what else do we need
我们的两个记录以及我们还需要什么
we need to I think that's it I think
我们需要我认为就是这样
that's actually oh you need we probably
那实际上是哦，您可能需要我们
need a content type right so with header
需要正确的内容类型，以便带有标题
HTTP headers dot content type media type
HTTP标头点内容类型媒体类型
equals application JSON utf-8 value and
等于应用程序JSON utf-8值，并且
that should be it that should be a very
应该是应该是一个非常
simple interaction we should have two
简单的互动，我们应该有两个
records if we run the test again
记录我们是否再次运行测试
everything should be golden ingredient
一切都应该是黄金成分
right very good so now let's be a little
对非常好，现在让我们来一点
bit more demanding let's make sure we're
要求更高一点，让我们确保我们
marshalling data back and forth
来回整理数据
correctly so let's say that the the data
正确地说，数据
we're going to store this in a
我们将其存储在
collection first of all we'll do we
首先我们要收集
reference it and use it as a variable so
引用它并将其用作变量，以便
customers there we go and now we're
客户去那里，现在我们
gonna say collection I say customers dot
要说收藏我说顾客点
customers dot iterator dot next dot get
客户点迭代器点下一个点得到
ID equals one L right and we're gonna
ID等于一个L对，我们要
say the first one will be Jane right so
说第一个是简，所以
you can see that we've got these a very
您可以看到我们已经将这些
convenient assert J api's these
方便的断言J api的这些
disfluent tests so that's been very
流利的测试，所以一直非常
convenient here because I'm exploring
这里方便，因为我正在探索
the API exploring the tests I just hit
探索我刚打过的测试的API
control space and the test basically
基本控制空间和测试
write themselves alright looks like
写自己看起来不错
things are working as we expect right
事情正在按预期进行
and so we know that there's two records
所以我们知道有两个记录
we know that the first one has the data
我们知道第一个有数据
that we expected to so I have no reason
我们期望如此，所以我没有理由
to doubt that the second one wouldn't
怀疑第二个不会
also have that okay so very good so now
也有很好，所以现在很好
we have a client and a service and might
我们有客户和服务，可能
be enough you know might be enough
足够，你知道可能就足够
why are mock certainly helps us here if
为什么模拟当然可以帮助我们，如果
it's if that API stays stable then this
如果该API保持稳定，那么这
won't be a big problem will it because
不会有什么大问题，因为
we can just use this wire mark stub and
我们可以使用这个电线标记存根
we know that we got it right this time
我们知道这次我们做对了
so as long as it doesn't change I think
所以只要不改变
we'll be okay the trouble of course is
我们会没事的，当然，麻烦是
that why not that API is a will change
那为什么不该API会改变
they'll change a lot and when they do
他们会改变很多，当他们这样做
change we run the risk of this no longer
改变，我们不再会有这种风险
being valid and additionally the
是有效的，另外
producer may not know that they've
制片人可能不知道他们已经
broken the experience that certain
打破了一定的经验
customers or clients rather have a start
客户或客户宁愿有一个开始
decided to become accustomed to that
决定习惯
they started to expect so they will
他们开始期望，所以他们会
happily merely evolve their service and
快乐地发展他们的服务，
perhaps unnecessarily and accidentally
也许是不必要和偶然的
break the the interactions that clients
打破客户之间的互动
have so this is not ideal for either
有所以这都不理想
side we know if there's what we need is
方面，我们知道是否有需要
some way to sort of catalog in that
在某种程度上分类目录
scenario that interaction and ensure
交互并确保的场景
that both sides agree on the definition
双方都同意这个定义
of that interaction that that scenario
在那种情况下的互动
and this is what consumer driven
这就是消费者驱动的
contract testing or you know contracts
合同测试或您知道合同
give us right we have a project in in
给我们权利，我们有一个项目正在
the spring portfolio called spring cloud
春季投资组合称为春季云
contract spring cloud contract gives us
合同spring-cloud-contract给了我们
the ability to describe a scenario this
描述场景的能力
is not a schema let's be very clear
不是一个架构，让我们非常清楚
about that this is actually and it a
关于这实际上是一个
sort of documentation of how one client
有关如何一位客户的文档
expects to interact with our service so
希望与我们的服务互动
let's go back to our service here
让我们在这里回到我们的服务
and we've got this test that we've
我们已经完成了这项测试
written and this is this test asserts
书面，这是该测试断言
how we expect the structure of the of
我们如何期望的结构
the response to look you know from the
你从中知道的反应
producer side but again this we were in
生产者方面，但同样，我们在
the risk of this drifting out of sync
这种不同步的风险
with what clients actually expect so
客户的实际期望
let's write a can't let's capture what
让我们写一个不能让我们捕捉到什么
we expect to happen in a given test in a
我们希望在给定的测试中发生
given interaction today right now all
立即进行互动
right so I'm gonna use a document
对，所以我要使用文件
directory here when I say test resources
我说测试资源时的目录
contracts and we'll create a new
合同，我们将创建一个新的
contract which is just a GU VDSL so
合同，这只是GU VDSL，所以
should we turn all customers boovie and
我们应该把所有的顾客都放下吗？
this is a type safe DSL so I'm gonna say
这是一种类型安全的DSL，所以我要说
contract dot make and we're gonna
合约点制造，我们将
provide a description should return all
提供说明应返回所有
customers request is going to have a
客户要求将有一个
certain shape so we'll describe that
一定的形状，所以我们将描述
here and the response will have a
在这里，响应将有一个
certain shape so now just to give you
一定的形状，所以现在只是给你
kind of give you a little bit of a
有点给你一点
prelude a little bit of foreshadowing
前奏一点铺垫
here what we're doing is we're saying
在这里，我们在说
that down the line we want a test to be
我们希望进行测试
generated for us automatically based on
为我们自动生成
what's in the contents of this movie DSL
这部电影DSL的内容是什么
and that test will be run against our
该测试将针对我们
API in the same way that our actual test
API与我们的实际测试相同
that we the one that we just toiled over
那就是我们辛苦劳动的那个
a few minutes ago does right now so that
几分钟前现在就这样做了
test is going to capture all the same
测试将捕获所有相同的
things right it's going to capture how
正确的事情将捕获如何
we expect one interaction to work so
我们希望可以进行一次互动，因此
we're saying that we expect a request
我们是说我们期待一个请求
that goes to the four slash customers
四个斜线客户
endpoint of type get that has a certain
具有一定确定性的get类型的端点
you know it could have a certain
你知道它可能有一定的
collection of headers we expect that
标头集合，我们希望
kind of request to yield a response that
产生回应的一种请求
looks like this it's gonna have a status
看起来像这样
of type 200 it'll have a header maybe of
类型200的标题可能是
content type right so we can say headers
内容类型正确，所以我们可以说标题
header HTTP headers content type media
标头HTTP标头内容类型媒体
type the equals application JSON you tip
输入您提示的等于应用程序JSON
it value and the body will be either a
它的价值和身体将是一个
map you know J sent the map that we can
您知道的地图J发送了地图，我们可以
be turned into a JSON structure it'll be
变成JSON结构
a literally an object value that we can
从字面上看，我们可以
produce back a list you know almost any
产生出您几乎知道的任何清单
number of different things you can even
你甚至可以做很多不同的事情
return just a string but in our case I'm
只返回一个字符串，但在我们这里，我是
okay with just which
好的，哪一个
a collection of maps right so that's the
正确的地图集合，这就是
syntax here yes but actually this is a
语法在这里，但是实际上这是一个
list but what we're doing is we're
列表，但我们正在做的是
creating a map we're cutting a list of
创建地图，我们将切割
objects dynamic maps so we can use the
对象动态地图，因此我们可以使用
goofy syntax here we're gonna say ID 1 L
高飞语法，在这里我们要说ID 1 L
and then surname or name is it let's see
然后是姓或名，让我们看看
what we have here name so I would go to
我们在这里有什么名字，所以我会去
the code they'll be called the name and
他们将被称为名称和
the first one will be called Jane and
第一个叫简和
we'll create another record ID 2 and
我们将创建另一个记录ID 2，
name is equal to Bob all right so
名字等于鲍勃，好吧，所以
returning this data this is not actual
返回此数据是不实际的
data it's data that we're expecting for
数据是我们期望的数据
our tests right again and that implies
我们的测试再次正确，这意味着
that we're gonna need to act you know do
我们将需要采取行动，你知道吗
the same sort of work as we did before
与以前一样的工作
to mock out the data access repository
模拟数据访问存储库
because this is going to actually call
因为这实际上是在打电话
our REST API in the same way that we
REST API的方式与
have done before with the mock MVC
之前已经完成了模拟MVC
client right so we need to make sure
客户权利，所以我们需要确保
that this mock interaction is captured
该模拟互动被捕获
right we need to set this up somewhere
对，我们需要在某个地方进行设置
so let's go configure the build process
让我们来配置构建过程
to respect these contracts and treat
尊重这些合同并对待
them as tests indeed to generate tests
他们作为测试确实可以生成测试
from them and this mechanism is why we
从他们那里，这种机制就是为什么我们
say this is a contract because the
说这是合同，因为
contract is kept by enforcing on compile
通过执行编译来保持合同
on build that the API works as expected
在构建中，API可以按预期工作
right we can't install or deploy our
对，我们无法安装或部署我们的
service if these contracts aren't
如果这些合同不是服务
passing and similarly clients won't be
过去，客户也不会
able to consume a the the definitions of
能够消耗一个的定义
the contract if they haven't been able
合同，如果他们没有能力
to deploy it and install it so we're
部署并安装它，所以我们
gonna use a build plugin here called the
将在这里使用一个名为
spring cloud contract plugin right so
Spring Cloud Contract插件对吧
here we go spring cloud I suppose we
在这里，我们去春天的云，我想我们
need the art group idea first so or
首先需要艺术小组的想法或
explain framework cloud spring cloud
解释框架云春季云
contract maven plugin and we need a
合约Maven插件，我们需要一个
version we can say 1.1.1 release that's
我们可以说1.1.1版本是
fine
精细
and this has a few other bits of
还有其他一些
configuration the first thing we have to
配置我们要做的第一件事
do is configure that it works with
要做的就是配置它与
extensions sure and the other thing that
扩展肯定，另一件事是
we need to do is to give it an idea of
我们需要做的是给它一个想法
where to find a base class when I say
我说哪里可以找到基类
base class what I mean is we need some
基类我的意思是我们需要一些
class that this dynamic
这个动态的类
generated tests these dynamically
生成动态测试
generated tests that were going to
生成的测试将
create well will extend right so we need
创造良好将延伸正确，所以我们需要
some sort of base class that it can
可以的某种基类
extend and in which we can do any kind
扩展，我们可以做任何事情
of sort of test setup so let's create a
各种测试设置，让我们创建一个
base class for tests and we'll create a
测试的基础类，我们将创建一个
new base class here Java base class here
这里的新基类这里的Java基类
we go so this is our base class and well
我们去，所以这是我们的基础课
we'll revisit this in a second but let's
我们将在稍后再讨论，但让我们
make sure we finish our thought here so
确保我们在这里完成想法
calm the example dot customer service
淡化示例点客户服务
base class alright so we've got that in
基类很好，所以我们已经有了
place now we need to actually implement
现在我们需要实际实施
that base class that base class will be
该基类将是的基类
a spring boot test it'll be run with
一个弹簧启动测试，它将与
this spring runner right so we're going
这个春天的跑步者，所以我们要去
to use that and we're going to auto
使用它，我们将自动
configure mock can BC that's fine
配置模拟可以BC很好
actually don't need I don't think we
实际上不需要我不认为我们
even need to do that we do have to do
甚至需要这样做，我们必须要做
some setup though don't we we need to
一些设置，虽然不是，我们需要
set up the the rest assured testing
设置放心的测试
right we're not using standards the the
对，我们没有使用标准
base the tests themselves don't use the
根据测试本身不使用
standard mock MVC spring a machinist a
标准的模拟MVC spring机械师a
Prada they use the integration with rest
他们使用Prada与其余部分整合
assured so it's not hard to set up would
放心，所以设置起来并不难
you say you need to say
你说你需要说
rest assured maka MVC standalone setup
放心maka MVC独立安装
you can pass in web application context
您可以在Web应用程序上下文中传递
you can pass in a single controller that
您可以传递一个控制器
should be used or configures you can do
应该使用或配置您可以做的
all sorts of things here I like to use
我喜欢在这里使用各种各样的东西
this timeout standalone set up and then
此超时独立设置，然后
just inject the repository under tests
只是注入测试中的存储库
so I'll say private customer rest
所以我会说私人客户休息
controller and we'll say this dot
控制器，我们将说这个点
customer rest controller and then we
客户 rest controller ，然后我们
need to do the same kind of setup that
需要进行相同的设置
we did before them the mocking of the
我们在他们面前做了嘲笑
data tier right so let's go to the test
数据层正确，让我们进行测试
from before and just borrow this bit
从以前开始，只是借用这一点
here and we're gonna mock out when use a
在这里，当我们使用
mock bean for the custom repository so
用于自定义存储库的模拟bean，因此
we'll go to our base class okay
我们去基础课好
and we'll use a at mock bean private
我们将使用at模拟 bean private
customer repository very good so there's
客户资料库非常好，所以
our basic setup our basic tests and now
我们的基本设置我们的基本测试
we can run this code one more time
我们可以再运行一次此代码
or we can't run it actually we have to
否则我们实际上无法运行它
run the code on the by running the
通过运行运行代码
compiler right so we go to the command
编译器正确，所以我们转到命令
line here and we'll do maven clean
在这里排队，我们将做清理
install that's more than enough and in
安装就足够了
the meantime we don't actually need this
同时，我们实际上并不需要这个
test I wrote this test but it turns out
测试我写了这个测试，但是结果
it's pointless so let's get rid of that
这是没有意义的，让我们摆脱它
and we'll start that compilation again
我们将再次开始编译
maven clean install ok so we ran the
行家干净安装好，所以我们跑了
test we didn't find a we didn't give our
测试我们没有找到我们没有给我们
test our base class enough information
测试我们的基类足够的信息
for it to find the spring application
找到弹簧应用程序
context so we go back to our base class
上下文，所以我们回到基础课
here here and we say that the class that
在这里，我们说的是
it should use is a customer service
它应该使用的是客户服务
application dot class go back here again
应用程序点类再次回到这里
all right looks like it's alright so
好吧，看起来还好，所以
that's our our contract now we can again
那是我们的合同，现在我们可以再次
we should prove the negative let's go
我们应该证明负面因素吧
back to the the let's go back to the
回到我们回到
code here and change Jane to Janet do a
在这里编写代码，然后将Jane更改为Janet，
maven clean install again
maven再次干净安装
and you can see that it failed and if
您会看到它失败了，如果
you look at what happened there's a test
你看看发生了什么，有一个测试
here that is an error contract verifier
这是一个错误合同验证程序
test so if you go to that cat contract
测试一下，如果你去那只猫合同
verifier test or cat target i'll here CD
验证程序测试或猫目标，我将在这里安装CD
target find i name contract verifier
目标找到我命名合同验证者
test right and we look at the last one
测试正确，我们看看最后一个
grip java cat script Java okay
抓取Java猫脚本Java可以
so cat this one and you can see that
所以猫这一个，你可以看到
it's actually a test that was generated
这实际上是生成的测试
for this contract verify test it extends
对于此合同，验证测试将其扩展
the base class and each test method
基类和每种测试方法
corresponds to a contract you can have
对应于您可以拥有的合约
one or ten or a thousand contracts that
一，十或一千份合同
describes certain scenarios certain
描述某些情况
interactions all the stuff that you'd
与您互动的所有内容
expect to be here is here right so it
期望在这里就在这里，所以
it's saying that were expecting response
就是说期待着回应
to come back that has a status code
回来，上面有一个状态码
equal to 200 the headers are equal to
等于200的标头等于
the following and we're using JSON path
以下，我们正在使用JSON路径
to interrogate the structure of the
审问
object that comes back from the service
从服务返回的对象
so this is basically testing exactly
所以这基本上是测试
what we tested before it's exactly the
我们测试之前，正是
same thing as what we tested in our in
与我们在测试中所做的相同
our previous test it's just that it's
我们之前的测试只是
done forth automatically and we get that
自动完成，我们得到了
for free but this would and that would
是免费的，但这会而且那会
be interesting in of itself because I
本身就很有趣，因为我
think this is actually a fair bit easier
认为这实际上有点容易
to understand and read than the test
比测试更了解和阅读
code that I wrote but this is this
我写的代码，但这是这个
actually has another much more promising
实际上还有另一个更有希望的
benefit which is that I can now export
好处是我现在可以出口
these these contracts so let's go ahead
这些合同，让我们继续
and fix our test and make sure that
并修复我们的测试，并确保
things work as we expect okay so Jane
事情按我们预期的那样很好，所以简
will be Jane will do a maven clean
会简做一个行家清洁
install one more time
再安装一次
maven clean install
Maven全新安装
all right so now we've installed
好吧，现在我们已经安装
everything and everything is green you
一切都是绿色的你
can see here that there's been three
可以看到这里有三个
installations installing custom service
安装安装定制服务
snapshot jar installing customer service
快照jar安装客户服务
snapshot palm and finally this is where
快照手掌，最后这是
it gets interesting
它变得有趣
installing customer service snapshot
安装客户服务快照
stubs jar the stubs that jar is the
存根是存根是
artifact of the plugin that we're using
我们正在使用的插件的工件
the maven plugin for spring cloud
Spring Cloud的Maven插件
contract the stub contains a JSON
合约存根包含JSON
document so if we go here jar xvf
文档，所以如果我们去这里jar xvf
customer service stub jar and you can
客户服务存根罐，您可以
see meta incom example customer service
请参阅meta incom示例客户服务
mappings cat should return all customers
映射猫应该返回所有客户
done JSON this is the native
完成JSON，这是本机
configuration file format for wire mock
电线模拟的配置文件格式
so we can we can we've encoded we've
这样我们就可以编码了
captured the the contract that you
捕获了您的合同
provided that we provided and we've used
只要我们提供并且我们已经使用
that to turn it into a wire mock
把它变成电线模拟
document which we can then feed into
然后我们可以输入的文件
well anything that supports wire mark
以及任何支持电线标记的东西
already so we can use that in the client
已经可以在客户端使用了
to stand up a fake API that looks and
站起来的假API看起来和
acts like the API that we described in
就像我们在
our DSL so let's do that we can go to
我们的DSL，让我们去吧
our client now over here and go back to
我们的客户现在在这里，然后返回
our build and remember in our build
我们的构建并记住我们的构建
we've already got spring cloud starter
我们已经有了Spring Cloud Starter
contract stub runner so we can go here
合同存根转轮，所以我们可以去这里
to our test and all we want to do is use
测试，我们要做的就是使用
the stub runner to stand up a fake API
存根赛跑者站起来假API
so we don't need wire mock anymore all
所以我们不再需要电线模拟了
right we can actually I mean we could
对，我们实际上可以，我的意思是我们可以
use JSON but we don't actually need that
使用JSON，但我们实际上并不需要
so what we need is auto configured step
所以我们需要的是自动配置的步骤
runner and our job now is to specify to
跑步者，我们现在的工作是指定
the stub Runner where to find the stub
存根赛跑者在哪里找到存根
definition that we need in order for us
我们需要的定义
to be able to run this test so let's
能够运行此测试，所以让我们
comment at all the bits we don't need we
在我们不需要的所有地方发表评论
can say IDs equal and work offline
可以说ID相等并且可以离线工作
equals true work offline means it's
等于真正的离线工作意味着
gonna look for the stubs in the local m2
会在当地m2中寻找存根
repository not just in maven central or
仓库不仅在Maven Central或
artifactory or whatever other
人工制品或其他
repositories you've got in your
您拥有的存储库
environment and the IDs that's the the
环境和ID
maven coordinates the maven style
Maven协调Maven风格
coordinates or the
坐标或
Ivy coordinates or whatever you know the
常春藤坐标或任何你知道的
the syntax for resolving that particular
解决该特定问题的语法
definition that stub jar that we just
定义我们只是存根罐
created so it's gonna be calm example :
创建，所以它会很平静的例子：
customer - service : and then we're
客户服务：然后我们
supposed to provide a version well of
应该提供一个很好的版本
course by definition what we want as a
当然，从定义上讲，我们希望
client is to get the latest successfully
客户要成功获取最新信息
deployed and produced stub definition so
部署并生成存根定义，以便
if that test hadn't passed then we
如果那个测试没有通过，那么我们
wouldn't have been able to run maven
不可能运行Maven
clean install you can imagine doing
全新安装，您可以想象
maven clean deploy and a real thing but
行家干净部署和真实的东西，但
suffice it to say we have another local
足以说我们还有另一个本地人
man m2 repository and either way whether
man m2存储库，以及是否
it's deployed and some other repository
它已部署，还有其他一些存储库
a local one we want to make sure that we
我们要确保我们本地
always have the latest and greatest stub
总是有最新最好的存根
definition because that represents the
定义，因为那代表
code that's in production presumably
大概在生产中的代码
right if I've may even clean deployed my
对，如果我什至可以干净地部署我的
my API then I've hopefully if you're
我的API，那么我希望您能
doing continuous delivery also deploy
连续交付也可以部署
that into production and I want to make
投入生产，我想
sure that my client matches whatever is
确保我的客户匹配任何
in production so I'm going to say plus
在生产中，我要说的是
that means the latest one and then I'm
这意味着最新的，然后我
gonna tell it to run this service on a
会告诉它在
port 8081
端口8081
right and that matches the reality of
正确的，符合现实
what we're trying to do here right we're
我们在这里试图做的是
trying to say when the client calls HTTP
试图说出客户端何时调用HTTP
localhost 8080 one for such customers we
本地主机8080这样的客户我们
want some data to come back alright so
希望一些数据回来，所以
that should be okay we don't need this
没关系，我们不需要这个
anymore we're no longer trying to
不再是我们了
serialize the data ourselves now let's
现在我们自己序列化数据，让我们
just try it let's see what happens so
尝试一下，看看会发生什么
run a customer client test now I'm
我现在进行客户客户测试
expecting something to break let's see
期待有什么破坏，让我们看看
what we got there we go
我们到那里去了
so the difference the the field in the
所以不同的领域
client is different from the field in
客户与以下字段不同
the service we have surname in the
我们在其中拥有姓氏的服务
client and in the real thing in the
客户和真实的东西
service we have name so we know that one
服务，我们有名字，所以我们知道一个
of these is no longer is not valid it's
这些不再是无效的
never been valid but our tests were
从未有效过，但我们的测试是
green you might say you might proclaim
绿色，您可能会说您可能会宣布
and yes they were green but they were
是的，他们是绿色的，但他们是
they didn't reflect the reality of the
他们没有反映现实
situation the only way we could have
唯一的办法
caught that before was to do a proper
在做适当的事情之前就意识到
integration test and yes we have cloud
集成测试，是的，我们有云
computing technologies and yeah Cloud
计算技术和耶云
Foundry has a great reactive Java client
Foundry具有出色的反应式Java客户端
that you can
你能行
use to with Java code deploy all your
使用Java代码部署所有
applications stand them up scale them
应用程序将它们按比例放大
etc but even that will take them you
等，但即使那样会带你
know minute right you don't want to you
知道分钟，你不想对你
don't wanna be on the hook for that so
不想为此陷入困境
much better to find this kind of stuff
更好地找到这种东西
out really really quickly so now let's
真的非常快地退出，所以现在让我们
run this test one more time let's see
再运行一次测试，让我们看看
that that works oh yeah get name okay
那行得通哦，好吧，取名字好吧
hey look at that it worked huh so we
嘿，看它起作用了，所以我们
know that it we know that it worked in
知道我们知道它在
catching the integration issues because
捕获集成问题，因为
it wouldn't have succeeded that first
首先不会成功
time and we know that if the producer
时间，我们知道，如果生产者
changes their API in some way that
以某种方式更改其API
breaks our client we will capture that
破坏了我们的客户，我们将捕捉到
because we will always consume the
因为我们将永远消耗
latest and greatest stub definitions
最新和最好的存根定义
right so that is very convenient and
对，这样非常方便，
this helps me make it this means that
这有助于我做到这一点，这意味着
it's easy for us to write code that is
对我们来说编写代码很容易
quick right you can see that test ran in
快速的权利，您可以看到测试已运行
137 milliseconds it's quick it's concise
137毫秒，简洁明快
actually this is less code less
实际上这是更少的代码
cognitive overhead then then the other
认知开销然后另一个
thing and most importantly it's scalable
东西，最重要的是它是可扩展的
right so I can actually do this for all
对，所以我实际上可以为所有人做到这一点
of my services all my services can use
我所有服务可以使用的服务
contracts and in so doing they they I'm
合同，这样做，他们我
not one no longer required as a client
不再需要一个客户
to deploy every single service I can
部署我可以的每一项服务
just consume the contract and I know
只是消耗合同，我知道
that that is as good as the service
和服务一样好
because it's the same tests that the
因为它与
producer of the service is using to
服务的生产者习惯于
validate its own API so you know the the
验证自己的API，因此您知道
processor is running the contract and
处理器正在运行合同，并且
using that as a test harness and reusing
将其用作测试工具并重用
the contract as a test harness it's the
合同作为测试工具
same contract right now of course there
现在当然有相同的合同
are some of those there's some poor
有一些穷人
schlubs out there who aren't using
在外面不使用的人
spring and I've heard about these I
春天，我听说过这些
understand that those people exist so
了解那些人的存在
there is of course great support for
当然有很大的支持
running this - for using these stub
运行此-使用这些存根
definitions outside of a spring
春天之外的定义
environment it's so convenient just to
环境很方便
be able to say Auto configure stub
可以说自动配置存根
Runner and then for the lifetime of your
赛跑者，然后在你的一生中
test I have all the stubs in this
测试我有这个的所有存根
artifact stood up and exposed for you on
神器站起来为你揭露
a certain port but that said maybe
某个港口，但那也许
you're an iPhone developer maybe you're
您是iPhone开发人员，也许您是
an Android developer html5 developer and
一个Android开发人员html5开发人员，以及
you don't want to have to learn how to
你不想学习如何
make install and deploy Java services
进行安装和部署Java服务
any way at all right so for that you can
任何方式都可以，因此您可以
still take a manage of these stubs we
仍然要对这些存根进行管理
can go to our we can see the stubs we've
可以去我们我们可以看到我们的存根
seen that they're already there right so
看到他们已经在那里，所以
let's
让我们
now go to the desktop and you can use
现在转到桌面，您可以使用
what's called the the the stub runner
所谓的存根赛跑者
boot jar and I happen to have a version
启动罐，我碰巧有一个版本
of it downloaded so I'm gonna go to the
它的下载，所以我要去
directory here and I've got stubborn er
目录在这里，我很固执
boot jar right there and the syntax is
引导罐就在那里，语法是
easy you say Java nice jar step run your
轻松地说出Java漂亮的jar步骤即可运行
boot and you say stub runner dot IDs
开机，你说存根跑步者点ID
equals comm that example customer -
等于示例客户的通信-
service plus 8081 and you say stub
服务加8081，你说存根
runner dot work offline equals true and
离线运行亚军等于true，
you start it up just as simple as we did
您像我们一样简单地启动它
it before right
正确之前
so now this should start on port 8081
所以现在应该从端口8081开始
localhost 8080 81 customers and there's
本地主机8080 81位客户
our data our actual data that you know
我们的数据我们知道的实际数据
it's being driven by that stub and we
它是由那个存根驱动的，我们
can just as long as we know the
只要我们知道
coordinates and we can pass past that
坐标，我们可以越过
jar around nobody else needs to know
罐子周围没人需要知道
anything else they don't need to deploy
他们不需要部署的其他任何东西
our database and your services they
我们的数据库和您的服务
don't need to wait they don't have to
不需要等待，他们不必
have their own confounded cluster or
有自己的混杂集群
space or whatever they can just test
空间或他们可以测试的任何东西
locally iterate quickly and develop
在本地快速迭代并发展
alright it's worth understanding that
好吧，值得理解的是
while we've looked at how to test an API
我们已经研究了如何测试API
a REST API using spring cloud contract
使用Spring Cloud Contract的REST API
there's a number of other possibilities
还有许多其他可能性
you can use spring cloud contract to
您可以使用Spring Cloud Contract来
test messaging based microservices using
使用以下命令测试基于消息传递的微服务
the spring cloud stream or spring
春天的云流或春天
integration or camel you can use it to
整合或骆驼，您可以使用它来
mock out your service registry so
模拟出您的服务注册表，以便
imagine in all your spring cloud code
想象一下您所有的春季云代码
where you have the discovery client
您拥有发现客户端的位置
you've got spring cloud contract based
您已经基于Spring Cloud Contract
services or stubs that are being
正在进行的服务或存根
referenced by a mock service registry so
由模拟服务注册表引用，因此
now you can load balance across you know
现在，您可以在整个已知的负载均衡
your services that are actually
您的实际服务
themselves to stubs you don't have to
自己去存根，你不必
deploy the real thing so there's a lot
部署真实的东西，所以有很多
of options beyond what we've shown you
除了我们向您展示的以外，还有其他选择
here and indeed there's a whole other
在这里，实际上还有一个整体
workflow called consumer giving
工作流程称为消费者给予
contracts where you actually end up as a
您最终以合同形式
client you end up driving the evolution
客户最终推动了发展
of the API in this case we did that kind
在这种情况下，我们做到了
of but there's a whole approach that you
但是有一种整体方法
can see to this so a lot of a lot of
可以看到很多
benefits to using spring called
使用spring的好处
contracts and with that my friends
和我的朋友们签约
thanks very much for watching and we'll
非常感谢您的收看，我们会
see you next time
下次见
you
您